{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Enterprise Architecture",
    "Term": "Prefinals",
    "Title": "QUIZ REVIEWER",
    "LastModified": "18 November 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Elmer Felisilda"
    ],
    "References": [
      "PREFINALS REVIEWER"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "It invovles the dissemination of information to all stakeholders.",
      "answer": "Informing",
      "choices": [
        "Informing",
        "Validation",
        "Obtaining commitment",
        "Maintaining the model"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This modeling action can be done by adding specific details to existing elements.",
      "answer": "Refinement",
      "choices": [
        "Refinement",
        "Introduction",
        "Abstraction",
        "Translation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which statement best describes knowledge transformation?",
      "answer": "It is a situation where knowledge processes through different modeling processes while considering objectives and guidelines.",
      "choices": [
        "It is a situation where knowledge processes through different modeling processes while considering objectives and guidelines.",
        "It involves the condition and commitment of stakeholders on enterprise architecture.",
        "It depicts an enterprise architecture model in a specific manner based on the agreed perception of the individuals involved in the process",
        "It is the primary and essential models that are used in the transformation of knowledge."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a VALID statement about limiting the visual complexity of a model?",
      "answer": "Reduce the number of relations depicted in a model.",
      "choices": [
        "Reduce the number of relations depicted in a model.",
        "Reduce the complexity of the concepts.",
        "Reduce the enemies to pieces.",
        "Reduce the number of submodels inside the model."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a metaphorical direction that goes towards the internal composition of an element.",
      "answer": "Inwards",
      "choices": [
        "Inwards",
        "Upwards",
        "Sidewards",
        "Downwards"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "People tend to perceive a line as uninterruptedly establishing a direction based on their perspective. What principle of Gestalt Theory of Human Perception is being described?",
      "answer": "Continuity",
      "choices": [
        "Continuity",
        "Proximity",
        "Closure",
        "Similarity"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These pertain to the primary and essential models that are used in the transformation of knowledge in enterprise architecture modeling.",
      "answer": "Central Representations",
      "choices": [
        "Central Representations",
        "Knowledge Representations",
        "Knowledge Goals",
        "Central Transformation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This activity requires checking whether the key stakeholders agree that the viewpoints in the model are correct.",
      "answer": "Validation",
      "choices": [
        "Validation",
        "Obtaining commitment",
        "Maintaining the model",
        "Informing"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In relation to modeling activities, which of the following refers to establishing the purpose, scope, and focus of a model?",
      "answer": "It is a goal-driven activity wherein architects determine all possible stakeholders and the purpose of the model in relation to the stakeholders.",
      "choices": [
        "It is a goal-driven activity wherein architects determine all possible stakeholders and the purpose of the model in relation to the stakeholders.",
        "It serves as a guide in determining appropriate information to be included in the model.",
        "It involves requirements gathering, such as appropriate information, to create, structure, and visualize an enterprise architecture model.",
        "It uses the model representation to communicate with the stakeholders and evaluate whether the model and the visualization achieved the intended outcome."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following processes is related to documentation as a modeling action?",
      "answer": "Backtracking the previous state of a model.",
      "choices": [
        "Backtracking the previous state of a model.",
        "Creating/replacing an element so it matches the meaning of a concept from another language or context.",
        "Classify the newly introduced candidate element based on the concepts used in the model.",
        "Placing a fresh term for a concept or relation in the model."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "People tend to perceive comparable objects as though they belong together as a unit. What principle of Gestalt Theory of Human Perception is being described?",
      "answer": "Similarity",
      "choices": [
        "Similarity",
        "Proximity",
        "Closure",
        "Continuity"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "People tend to relate objects that are near to each other. What principle of Gestalt Theory of Human Perception is being described?",
      "answer": "Proximity",
      "choices": [
        "Proximity",
        "Similarity",
        "Closure",
        "Continuity"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This modeling action involves the administration and documentation of other modeling actions.",
      "answer": "Documentation",
      "choices": [
        "Documentation",
        "Translation",
        "Abandoing",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a modeling action?",
      "answer": "Abandoning a modeling language",
      "choices": [
        "Abandoning a modeling language",
        "Documentation",
        "Abandoning a concept",
        "Refinement"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following processes is related to refinement as a modeling action?",
      "answer": "Classifying newly introduced candidate elements based on the modeling concept",
      "choices": [
        "Classifying newly introduced candidate elements based on the modeling concept",
        "Backtracking the previous state of a model.",
        "Creating/replacing an element so it matches the meaning of a concept from another language or context.",
        "Placing a fresh term for a concept or relation in the model."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This pertains to the form in which a model is presented.",
      "answer": "Visualization",
      "choices": [
        "Visualization",
        "Model",
        "Representation",
        "Presentation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This depicts an enterprise architecture model based on the agreed perception of the individuals involved in the process.",
      "answer": "Knowledge Representation",
      "choices": [
        "Knowledge Representation",
        "Knowledge Goals",
        "Central Transformation",
        "Central Representations"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the act of placing a fresh term for a concept or relation within a model.",
      "answer": "Introduction",
      "choices": [
        "Introduction",
        "Refinement",
        "Abandoning",
        "Abstraction"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following processes is related to abandoning as a modeling action?",
      "answer": "Eliminating an element with proper documentation",
      "choices": [
        "Eliminating an element with proper documentation",
        "Can be done by adding specific details to existing elements.",
        "An architect decides whether information that is available in the model, is to be left out or not.",
        "Creating/replacing an element so it matches the meaning of a concept from another language or context."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the process of finding a suitable alternative for an element.",
      "answer": "Translation",
      "choices": [
        "Translation",
        "Documentation",
        "Refinement",
        "Introduction"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Gestalt Theory of Human Perception, which of the following scenarios pertain to common fate?",
      "answer": "People have the tendency to perceive different objects, which function in a similar manner, as a unit",
      "choices": [
        "People have the tendency to perceive different objects, which function in a similar manner, as a unit",
        "People have the tendency to perceive objects that are similar to belong together in a unit.",
        "Also known as 'tadhana'",
        "People have the tendency to perceive a line as continuous establishing directions based on their perspective."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "If modeling is considered a transformation process in enterprise architecture, which of the following statements is correct?",
      "answer": "Models can be used to describe the future situation of an organization",
      "choices": [
        "Models can be used to describe the future situation of an organization",
        "Goal-driven activity wherein architects determine all possible stakeholders and the different purposes of the model in relation to the stakeholders.",
        "Involves requirements gathering, such as appropriate information, to create, structure, and visualize an enterprise architecture model.",
        "Models are created using different viewpoints that give a specific set of concepts and relations to be used during the modeling process."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following is NOT a valid statement regarding modeling actions?",
      "answer": "Documentation is the process of finding a suitable alternative for an element",
      "choices": [
        "Documentation is the process of finding a suitable alternative for an element",
        "Stakeholders and their needs must be considered in visualizing a model.",
        "Uses the model representation to communicate with the stakeholders and evaluate whether the model and the visualization achieved the intended outcome.",
        "Models are created using different viewpoints that give a specific set of concepts and relations to be used during the modeling process."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Based on the modeling guidelines in enterprise architecture, which of the following is correct?",
      "answer": "Collect feedback from various stakeholders",
      "choices": [
        "Collect feedback from various stakeholders",
        "Use abstractions as frequent as possible.",
        "Introduce novel concepts and structures.",
        "Make the model such as it relies on additional explanation."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Gestalt Theory of Human Perception, which of the following scenarios pertains to closure?",
      "answer": "People have the tendency to perceive incomplete objects as complete",
      "choices": [
        "People have the tendency to perceive incomplete objects as complete",
        "People have the tendency to perceive objects that are similar to belong together in a unit.",
        "People have the tendency to perceive a line as continuous establishing directions based on their perspective.",
        "It's all in the past, pangga. Let's move on with our lives and let go of the past."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Relative to the representation conventions, which of the following best describes the use of layouts?",
      "answer": "This includes basic patterns, alignment, and object distribution",
      "choices": [
        "This includes basic patterns, alignment, and object distribution",
        "Shapes of objects in a model usually match the intrinsic properties of the real-life objects.",
        "Can also increase the appeal of a diagram but can also lead to contrary effects, such as confusion and distraction.",
        "Speeds up the creating of a proper mental state in modeling, while creating a good starting for the line of reasoning."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "If modeling is considered a transformation process in enterprise architecture, which of the following statement is INCORRECT?",
      "answer": "Enterprise architecture provides a high-level overview of an organization",
      "choices": [
        "Enterprise architecture provides a high-level overview of an organization",
        "Depicts an enterprise architecture model in a specific manner based on the agreed perception of the individuals involved in the process.",
        "Knowledge passes through the modeling process while considering goals and guidelines.",
        "Goals under the modeling process of an enterprise architecture."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This modeling activity utilize the model representation to communicate with the stakeholders and evaluate the model.",
      "answer": "Using the model",
      "choices": [
        "Using the model",
        "Visualizing the model",
        "Creating and structuring the model",
        "Establishing the purpose, scope, and focus"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This refers to a situation where knowledge passes through different modeling processes while considering objectives and guidelines.",
      "answer": "Knowledge transformation",
      "choices": [
        "Knowledge transformation",
        "Knowledge Goals",
        "Knowledge Representation",
        "Knowledge State"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is INCORRECT about modeling activities?",
      "answer": "Using a model requires validation",
      "choices": [
        "Using a model requires validation",
        "Requirements gathering is performed in model visualization.",
        "Enterprise architecture involves the identification of relationships between different domains while providing a high-level overview.",
        "Models can also be used to describe the current and future situation of an organization, as well as the possible development requirements."
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz Reviewer",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    }
  ]
}